Psi Gamma Sorority and Alumnae Association, Inc.; Records ua801.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Psi Gamma Sorority Records, 1989-1995; 1
  - Series 1: Psi Gamma Sorority Subject Files, 1898-1995; 1.1; 2 cubic ft.
    - Programs, Parents Banquet, 05/18/1969 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 40)
    - "Psi Gamma Screw" program, ca. 1968-1969 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 41)
    - Rush, 1955-1962 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 42)
    - Rush, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 43)
    - Rush, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 44)
    - Rush, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 45)
    - Rush, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 46)
    - Rush, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 47)
    - Rush, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 48)
    - Rush, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 49)
    - Rush, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 50)
      (includes Mary Patrick '71, pacifier).
    - Rush, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 51)
    - Rush, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 52)
    - Rush, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 53)
    - Rush, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 54)
    - Rush, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 55)
    - Rush, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 56)
    - Rush, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 57)
    - Rush, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 58)
    - Rush, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 59)
      Rush folders include songs, handbooks, schedules, questionnaires, and pledge books.
      See also pledge lists.
    - Self Evaluations, 1965-1970; 1982 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 60)
    - Songs, 1969-1993 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 61)
    - Spring Weekend, 1976; 1982 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 62)
    - Standing Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 63)
    - State University of New York at Albany: Rules and Regulations, 1974-1990 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 64)
    - Student Senate Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 65)
      See also Greek workshops.
    - Summer Planning Conference, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 66)
    - Supplies, 1971-1990 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 67)
    - Swanner, Grace Maguire '23, interview recorded on audio cassette, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 68)
    - Telethon, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 69)
    - Women's Handbook, 1962 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 70)
  - Series 2: Psi Gamma Sorority Scrapbook Collection, 1898-1995; 1.2; 4.8 cubic ft.
    Arranged chronologically within each sub-series.
    - Annual Scrapbooks, 1952-1995 (with gaps); 1.2.1; 2.4 cubic ft.
      This sub-series consists of scrapbooks compiled by the sorority over the course of 14 academic years. Academic years included in this sub-series are 1952-1953, 1956-1957, 1957-1958, 1961-1962, 1962-1963, 1963-1964, 1966-1967, 1968-1969, 1969-1970, 1970-1971, 1971-1972, 1974-1975, 1977-1978, and 1991-1992. Included in these scrapbooks are photographs of sorority life, newspaper articles, invitations to special events, correspondence, greeting cards, and announcements.
      Arranged chronologically.
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1962-1963 (Box 2 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1966-1967 (Box 3 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 4 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1974-1975 (Box 5 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1977-1978 (Box 5 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Scrapbook, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1.2.1-Annual Scrapbooks))
    - Anniversary Scrapbooks, 1898-1995 (with gaps); 1.2.2; 1 cubic foot
      This sub-series consists of scrapbooks compiled for Psi Gamma reunions. These scrapbooks commemorate the 1956, the 1988, and the 1995 reunions. Included in these scrapbooks are photographs taken at anniversaries, pictures of sorority life over the past hundred years, and facsimiles of composite photos taken from the State College yearbooks.
      - Psi Gamma Retrospective Scrapbook (vol. 1), 1898-1956 (Box 1 (1.2.2-Anniversary Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Retrospective Scrapbook, 1910s-1920s; 1938-1941; 1958-1979 (Box 1 (1.2.2-Anniversary Scrapbooks))
        Contains primarily photocopies of yearbook pictures, 1958-79.
        Also contains photos of Central Avenue House in the 1910s, 113 Lake Avenue House from the 192[0s?], candid photos of college life, 1938-41, and composite and group photographs, 1969, 1972, 1976.
      - Psi Gamma Ninetieth Anniversary Celebration Scrapbook, 1988 (Box 1 (1.2.2-Anniversary Scrapbooks))
      - Psi Gamma Retrospective Scrapbook, 1898-1995 (Box 1 (1.2.2-Anniversary Scrapbooks))
    - Sorority Member Scrapbooks, 1924-1928; 1930-1936; 1945; 1955; 1963-1972; 1.2.3; 1 cubic foot
      This sub-series consists of scrapbooks compiled by individual members of Psi Gamma Sorority. Items in this sub-series include photographs, newspaper articles, correspondence, invitations to social events, pins and other jewelry, and sorority familytree Scrapbooks were donated to the sorority by Helen Klady McCuen ('28), Bertha Buhl Covell ('33), Margaret Schlott Koeler ('45), and Kerry Ann White ('55). Included is one file of loose photos and negatives.
      - Helen Klady McCuen '28 Scrapbook, 1924-1928 (Box 1 (1.2.3-Sorority Member Scrapbooks))
      - Bertha Buhl Covell '33 Scrapbook, 1930-1936 (Box 1 (1.2.3-Sorority Member Scrapbooks))
      - Margaret Schlott Koeler Scrapbook, class of 1945, Undated (Box 1 (1.2.3-Sorority Member Scrapbooks))
      - Kerry Ann White Pledge Scrapbook, 1955 (Box 1 (1.2.3-Sorority Member Scrapbooks))
      - "Loose Photographs & negatives, some identifications", Undated; 1 file folder (Box 1 (1.2.3-Sorority Member Scrapbooks))
    - Foster Child Scrapbook, 1963-1972; 1.2.4; 0.4 cubic ft.
      This sub-series contains correspondence, information sheets, reports, and photographs. From 1963 through 1966, Psi Gamma sorority sponsored a Greek child named Gregory Stratakis through Foster Parents' Plan, Inc.. In 1966, they began sponsoring another Greek child named Pavlos Mamalakis, whom they continued to sponsor through 1972. This scrapbook documents the correspondence between the sorority, their foster children, and Foster Parents' Plan, Inc.
      - Foster Child Scrapbook, 1963-1972; 2 folders (Box 1 (1.2.4-Foster Child Scrapbook))
  - Series 3: Psi Gamma Sorority Ephemera, 1943-1993; 1.3; 3 cubic ft.
    This series consists of pins, ash trays, banners, beanies, stuffed animals, embroidery, sorority family trees, glass bowls, jackets, jugs, keys, mugs, pledge paddles, patches, rattles, leather shields, sweatshirts, and tee shirts. Many of these items are stored in a steamer style trunk that is painted blue with Psi Gamma written in red letters. Items of note include two silver platters, one silver tea server, one silver coffee server, one silver sugar container, one silver goblet engraved with the Psi Gamma Greek letters (broken), and one silver vase.
    No arrangement.
    - Banner, blue with "Psi Gamma" shield and sorority name spelled out in Greek, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Beanie with Psi Gamma Logo, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Brandy Snifter, blue and yellow "Psi Gamma" and "Betsy" written on it, [1981?] (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Compact for powder donated by Helen Kisiel Schick, class of 1948, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cup, wood with Psi Gamma engraving, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Display of jewelry (pins, lockets, ring) and jacket patch (blue tape edges, acrylic with a felt backing), Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      "Sister Pin with chain guard, donated by Marian Walker '40".
      "Lavaliere, donated by Sharon Kirsch '84".
      "Blazer Patch".
      "Wooden Pin, donated by Clarice Millspaugh".
      "Gold Pledge Pin".
      "Ring and Necklace".
      "Gold Shield".
      "Forget-Me-Not Pledge Pin attached to Charm, donated by Mildred Tymeson Young '45".
      "Locket with Mother of Pearl and Forget-Me-Not Center, donated by Janet Letteron '45".
    - Dog with Psi Gamma Logo, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Dog with Psi Gamma Logo, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Dr. Grace Maguire Swanner Distinguished Alumni Award poster, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Jacket, teal with Psi Gamma patch sewn in gold thread, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Key, with initials H.L., Psi Gamma Rose Suite, Room 1, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Moonshine Jugs (3), brown glass jug within a tan ceramic cup with "Psi Gamma" shield, 70th anniversary souvenir, 1968 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Mug, wooden, with "Psi Gamma" and "State College at Albany" inscriptions, donated by Millie Foote Frandino, class of 1953, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Patch, teal leather, with Psi Gamma letters, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Patch, light blue wool with yellow Psi Gamma letters & "Psi Gamma" written in Greek, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Picture frame, acrylic, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pins, (7) boxed, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      (see also display of jewelry and jacket patch above).
    - Pledge Paddle, from Linda '70 to Jill '69, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddle, with "CONNIE" written in black letters, 1971 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddle, from Myra '81 to Maureen '78, [1981?] (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddle, inscribed "Betsy '81" and "Candy '79", [1981?] (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddles (2), "Spring Weekend 1966", red stained wood, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddle, inscribed "Gerry, love, Maryjo, 1968" cream paint with blue/gold lettering, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Pledge Paddle, inscribed "Psi Gamma Fall 2002, Sister, Kristen, Me So Horny, Shady, Raver, Iota, Rho", gift of Kristen DeLotto, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Silver table ware, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      2 trays, 1 vase, 1 sugar container, 1 goblet engraved "Psi Gamma" and "Sandie" (broken).
    - State College Song Book, 1929 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Sweat shirt with "PSI GAMMA" spelled out in Greek, light blue with gold lettering, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Moonshine Doll, Psi Gamma mascot, tan bear with light blue vest and cap, Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Moonshine Doll, Psi Gamma mascot, tan bear with navy blue vest & hat with Psi Gamma Ribbon, Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Rattle, light blue and white with Psi Gamma letters written in gold, Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Yarn Octopus Doll With two buttons, "I love NY" and "Be a Neighbor", Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ash trays (2), from 75th Anniversary, 1973 (Box 3 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Bowl, glass (small) with Psi Gamma letters leaded on outside, Undated (Box 3 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Rush candy box and "Rush Psi Gamma" Button, 1993 Spring (Box 3 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Tee shirt, gold, with Psi Gamma logo and "Prez" written in blue, Undated (Box 4 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Tee shirt, white, "Psi Gamma 1982 Spring Weekend", Undated (Box 4 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Tee shirt, "85th Anniversary", [1983] (Box 4 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cover for initiation ceremony, teal leather with Psi Gamma letters & black background, Undated; 10" × 18" Digital Files (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cover for initiation ceremony, leather, teal & gold with Psi Gamma letters, Undated (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cover for initiation ceremony, leather, brown with PSI Gamma letters burned in, Undated; 11" × 16" Digital Files (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Embroidered Place Mat with Psi Gamma letters & blue bird, Undated (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Family Tree, [1977?] (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      With names Jo Anne Bhler '47, Pat Kenny "??, Laurie Governali '74, Donna Hughes '75, Patty Helback '77, Nancy Kalln '77, and Joyce Belza '77.
    - Shield, leather, with STATE in block letters, Psi Gamma letters, and '43, Undated (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Donated by Clarice Millspaughey Company, ca. 1929.
    - Shield, small, white leather background with teal Psi Gamma letters, Undated (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Shield, white leather background, PSI Gamma letters, and '45, Undated; 11" × 16" Digital Files (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Shield, teal leather background, Psi Gamma spelled out, STATE, & Greek inscription, Undated; 16" × 20" Digital Files (Box 5 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Scholarship Award Plaque, 1964-1970; 1980 (Box 6 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Blazer, light blue, with Psi Gamma embroidery on pocket, Gift of Carol Bostok, class of 1961, Undated (Box 7 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Banner, "State College" shield, light blue with gold border, Undated; 13" × 17.5" Digital Files (Box 8 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Banner, shield, navy blue, Undated; 34" × 59" Digital Files (Box 8 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Banner, shield, royal blue, Undated; 38" × 52" Digital Files (Box 8 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Banner, "Psi Gamma-A Step Above the Rest", black with footprints, Undated (Box 9 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Banner, "If You Need a Helping Hand", Undated (Box 9 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Family Tree, OO through OT pledge classes, Undated (Box 9 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Silver table ware: 1 coffee server, 1 tea server, Undated (Box 10 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Oversize Ephemera, Undated
      Display of pins and rings.
  - Series 4: Psi Gamma Sorority Composite Photographs, 1951-2002 (with gaps); 1.4; 0.4 cubic ft.
    This series consists of formal composite photographs that portray each member of the sorority during the following academic years: 1951-1952, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, 1989-1990, 1990-1991, 1991-1992, 1992-1993, 1993-1994 (Stony Brook), 1994-1995, and 2001-2002.
    - Composite Photograph, 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
      Gift of Linda Kroell '66.
    - Composite Photograph, 1964 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1966 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, Stony Brook, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Composite Photograph, Gift of Kristen DeLotto, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
  - Series 5: Psi Gamma Sorority Guest Books, 1948-1998 (with gaps); 1.5; 0.33 cubic ft.
    This series is composed of five guest books for the years 1948-1955, 1969-1972, 1972-1973, 1991, and 1998. The guest books record the signatures, addresses, phone numbers, and remarks of persons attending alumnae luncheons, open houses, punch parties, conflict parties, coker receptions, and crush parties. Of particular note is the "Golden Anniversary" guest book celebrating Psi Gamma's 50th anniversary.
    Guest books record attendance at social functions such as Golden Anniversaries.
    - Open Houses, Punch Parties, Conflict Parties, Coker Receptions, etc., Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Guest Book, 1948-1955 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Guest Book, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Guest Book, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Guest Book, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Guest Book, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
  - Series 6: Psi Gamma Sorority Financial Records, 1927-1991 (with gaps); 1.6; 0.66 cubic ft.
    This series consists of bank reconciliation statements, cash books, checking account registers, dues registers, and ledgers. The cash books (1950-1959) and registers (1927-1938, 1958-1962, 1974-1977, 1979-1980, and 1987-1991) record Psi Gamma income and expenditures. Checking account registers (1958-1964) and bank reconciliation statements (1959-1960) document Psi Gamma bank account activity, and dues registers (1979-1980) record which sisters have and have not paid their dues.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Bank Reconciliation Statements, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cash Book, 1950-1954 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Cash Book, 1955-1959 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1958 March 29-1959 April 16 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1959 April 27-1960 February 29 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1960 April 5-1961 February 20 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1961 February 21-1962 March 6 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1962 March 6-1963 May 6 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Checking Account Registers, 1963 May 7-1964 April 28 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Dues Register, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1927-1938 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1958-1962 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Ledger, 1987-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
- Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records, 1922-1997; 2
  - Series 1: Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Subject Files, 1922-1997 (with gaps); 2.1; 0.66 cubic ft.
    This series consists of correspondence, minutes, newsletters, constitutions, membership lists, and video cassettes. The annual and executive board meeting minutes, (1922-1956), annual meeting minutes (1956-1995, missing 1971-1973, 1975-1981, and 1985-1986), and the board of directors minutes (1971, 1981-1995, missing 1982, 1984, and 1986) record the quarterly meetings of the executive board and the annual meetings of the association. The alumnae newsletters (1952-1997) are quarterly publications that inform alumnae members of upcoming and past alumnae events. The newsletters also list the activities of alumnae members, Psi Gamma Sorority events, meeting minutes, budget reports, and other issues that might be of interest to alumnae members. The constitution (1924-1993), which was recently amended in 1993, documents the association's mission statement and rules for organization. Finally, the association regularly provides detailed information about members' addresses and phone numbers in the membership lists (1922-1983) and officer lists (1988-1995).
    Of particular note in this series is the Edna Shaffer MacAffer award file (1924-1992) that contains MacAffer's biographical information as well as information about the annual award named in her honor. Also of note is the video recording of the 1994 annual meeting, where Grace Maguire Swanner was honored an a distinguished alumni and each alumnae member briefly introduced herself in front of everyone attending the reunion.
    Alumnae Newsletters include upcoming and recent sorority and alumnae activities, activities of alumnae members, meeting minutes, and president's letters.
    See also annual and executive meeting minutes.
    - Alumnae Newsletters, 1952-1980 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 1)
    - Alumnae Newsletters, 1981-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting/Luncheon Correspondence and reservations, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting/Luncheon Correspondence and reservations, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting/Luncheon Correspondence and reservations, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting/Luncheon Correspondence and reservations, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Video Cassette, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 7)
      Includes award for Grace Maguire Swanner and introductions from all attending members.
    - Constitution, 1924-1993 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 8)
    - Edna Shaffer MacAffer Award, 1924-1992 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 9)
      Includes biographical information about MacAffer, description of award, and award letters.
    - Membership Lists, 1898-1983 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Annual and Executive Board Meeting, 1922-1956 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 11)
      Annual and executive meeting minutes include discussions on housing, anniversary meetings, and purchases for active sorority.
      See also alumnae newsletters.
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1956-1970 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 5)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 6)